eventil.com 2019-06-22

# Events for Tech People · Eventil

By using eventil.com (the “Website”) and/or a Eventil account (the “Service”), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the [Terms of Service](https://eventil.com/terms). Eventil is designed and operated by Te2 Sp. z o.o. (“Te2”). Please read the Terms of Service in their entirety, and refer to those for definitions and contacts.

All personal data that we collect providing you with our services remain under our special care. Below you will find the explanation of issues related to ensuring security for your personal data in the form of answers to the following questions:

### GDPR compliance

For a detailed list of data sub-processors under the GDPR please see below under “Sharing of Data”.

#### Your Data Protection Rights Under The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are a resident of the EEA, you have the following data protection rights:

  * You can object to the processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict the processing of your personal information, or request portability of your personal information. You can exercise these rights by emailing [hello@eventil.com](mailto:hello@eventil.com).
  * You have the right to opt-out of marketing communications we send you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the “unsubscribe” or “opt-out” link in the marketing emails we send you. To opt-out of other forms of marketing, please contact us by emailing [hello@eventil.com](mailto:hello@eventil.com).
  * Similarly, if we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
  * You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority.

#### Right to Access, Correct, Update, or Request Deletion of Data

If you want to request an export or deletion of your personal data, and have an account with us, please contact us at [hello@eventil.com](mailto:hello@eventil.com). Please note that we cannot delete personal data in open accounts when you’re not the account owner, as this would prevent us from providing the service the account owner is paying for (We suggest that you contact the account owner of the Eventil account in question to ask them to anonymize or remove your data).

In order to accommodate customers who need older data restored, we keep backups indefinitely and cannot delete personal data form them as these are stored off-site, read-only and heavily encrypted and compressed. If we do have access or restore data to our production systems or for purposes of debugging, any deletions of personal data will be applied retroactively or the personal data will be anonymized.

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

#### International data transfers

GDPR includes provisions on international data transfer mechanisms. In order to comply with these provisions we have certified under the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield frameworks (please see below for details).

#### Data Retention and Deletion Schedules

##### Application Data and Backups

Backups are securely encrypted and stored as defined in our Privacy Policy.

In order to accommodate customers who need older data restored, we keep backups indefinitely and cannot delete personal data form them as these are stored off-site, read-only and heavily encrypted and compressed. If we do have access or restore data to our production systems or for purposes of debugging, any deletions of personal data will be applied retroactively or the personal data will be anonymized.

##### Purchase Records and Invoices for our Services and Products

We keep copies of all purchasing records for tax and auditing purposes.

##### Personal Metadata

We keep personal metadata, given that the user allows us to process their data

We will also respond to Data Subject Rights Requests within the appropriate amount of time

##### Metadata collected by 3rd-party services

Some 3rd party services collect data independently from us, and have incorporated it as part of their service.

We do not store any copies of this data, and Data Subject Requests for this data must be submitted to the 3rd party service, since we do not control the data.

##### Te2’s Internal Business Data

We keep all internal business data as long as it’s relevant, and internal business data may include the data listed above.

#### Data Processing Agreement

We do have a Standard Data Processing Addendum ([DPA](https://eventil.com/gdpr-dpa)), which meets with GDPR requirements for agreements between Data Controllers (you) and Data Processors (us). We offer this DPA to our customers that operate in the EU. The DPA offers contractual terms that meet GDPR requirements and reflect our data privacy and security commitments to our clients. To ensure no inconsistent or additional terms are imposed on us beyond that reflected in our standard DPA and model clauses, we cannot agree to sign customers’ DPAs. We’re a small team so we can’t offer individual changes to the DPA since we do not have a legal team on staff. Any changes to the standard DPA would require legal counsel that would be cost prohibitive, increase our prices and would put an undue burden on our other customers. The DPA is a part of our Terms of Service. By agreeing to our terms of service, you are automatically accepting our DPA and do not need to sign a separate document.

### Data Collected

We collect anonymous data from every visitor of the Website to monitor traffic and fix bugs. For example, we collect information like web requests, the data sent in response to such requests, the Internet Protocol address, the browser type, the browser language, and a timestamp for the request.

We use cookies to store session information for your convenience. Cookies must be enabled to use the Website and the Service.

In order to take advantage of certain features of the Service, you may also choose to provide us with other personal information, such as your picture, but your decision to utilize these features and provide such data will always be voluntary.

### Use of the Data

We only use your personal information to provide you with the Service to communicate with you about the Service or the Website. This includes both automated and manual processing of data.

With respect to any data you may choose to enter or upload to Eventil, we take the privacy and confidentiality of this data seriously. Your data (in the Service) is specifically not shared between accounts or with the public. We employ industry standard techniques to protect against unauthorized access of data that we store, including personal information. All off-site backups of your data are securely encrypted.

Please note that if you choose to share data (like sharing invoices with your clients), we are not responsible for any violation of privacy law you may be liable for.

We do not share personal information you have provided to us without your consent, unless:

doing so is appropriate to carry out a user’s request;

  * we believe it’s necessary in order to provide the highest quality of service;
  * we believe it’s needed to enforce our Terms of Service, or that is legally required;
  * we believe it’s needed to detect, prevent or address fraud, security or technical issues;
  * otherwise protect our property, legal rights, or that of others.

Eventil is operated from the Poland. If you are visiting the Website from Europe, you agree to any processing of any personal information you provide us according to this policy.

Eventil may contact you by email. For example, Eventil may send you promotional emails relating to Eventil or communicate with you about your use of the Eventil Website and Service. If you do not want to receive email from Eventil, please opt out of receiving emails at the bottom of any Eventil email. Please note that for some emails (for example billing issues), there’s no option to opt-out.

### Sharing of Data

We don’t share your personal information with third parties except as listed below. Other then the information outlined below, only aggregated, statistical data is periodically transmitted to external services to help us improve the Eventil Website and Service.

For client-side analytics and tracking beacons, you’re welcome to use content blocking software; just be aware that this may influence our ability to identify errors and performance problems in your account. We can’t guarantee that Eventil will work as intended when browser extensions alter the HTML, CSS or JavaScript code we transmit (however, we don’t take any active steps to prevent you from using extensions, including content blockers).

We currently use Stripe (billing service and credit card vault), Google Analytics, Mailgun (transactional emails), Sentry.io (error tracking);

We listed below what data these third parties extract exactly. Feel free to check out their own Privacy Policies to find out more.

**Tracking errors and measuring performance:**

  * Google Analytics: no personally identifiable data is shared ([Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy))
  * Sentry.io: does not include passwords or credit card information ([Privacy Policy](https://sentry.io/privacy/))

**Transactional emails (Billing-related emails, etc.):**

  * Mailgun: your name and email and account data inside emails ([Privacy Policy](https://www.mailgun.com/privacy-policy))

**Service hosting and data backups**

  * Amazon AWS: storing encrypted archives of backup data, avatars and import files. This data is not readable by Amazon AWS. ([Privacy Policy](https://aws.amazon.com/privacy/))
  * OVH: hosting of Eventil servers and databases including all customer data, but does not include credit card information. Some data, like passwords, is always encrypted by industry standard measures. ([Privacy Policy](https://www.ovh.co.uk/personal-data-protection/))

Additionally, Te2 uses third party vendors that provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage and other technology required to run the Website and the Service. While Te2 owns the rights to the Eventil Website and Service, you retain all rights to the data you enter into Eventil.

If Te2 is acquired or merged with an other company, or Te2 sells the Eventil Website and Service to an other company, or if Te2 goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information may be transferred to a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Te2 or its assets may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make any significant changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Website or sending you an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted.

### Questions

Should you have any question or concern, please write to [hello@eventil.com](mailto:hello@eventil.com)

If you need to contact a data privacy officer, please use the contact information above.
